Arch Oboler Collection
Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division, Library of Congress
- Series 9. Scripts, 1933-1993 and undated, 70 linear feet (168 boxes)
  - Radio, 1933-1981 and undated
    - "Rogue Male"
      - Town file, 1944 February (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - "Roughing It"
      - Fire file, 1944 January (Box 272, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1944 January (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - "Russian Front," fire and town files, 1943 May-June (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - "Sakhalin"
      - Fire file, 1937 March, 1943 August (Box 272, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1943 August (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - San Diego State College Radio
      - "Big Shot," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - "Hi, Grandma!" circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - "Johnny Got His Gun," 1965 April 14 (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - "Laughing Man," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 4)
      - "Lover," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 5)
      - "Mrs. Kingsley's Report," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 6)
      - "Naked Man," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 7)
      - "Night," 1965 April 13 (Box 273, Folder 8)
      - "Old Boy," 1965 April 15 (Box 273, Folder 9)
      - "Vicious Circle," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 10)
      - "What the Devil," circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 11)
      - Untitled and loose pages, circa 1965 (Box 273, Folder 12)
    - "Scoop"
      - Fire file, 1938 June, 1942 December (Box 273, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1938 June, 1942 December (Box 273, Folder 14)
    - "Screen Test"
      - Fire file, 1938 February, 1943 May (Box 273, Folder 15)
      - Town file, 1938 February, 1943 May (Box 273, Folder 16)
    - "The Sea"
      - Fire file, 1936 September, 1939 February, 1943 March (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1937, 1943 March (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - "See Miss Brennan"
      - Fire file, 1939 December, 1940 February, 1941 June (Box 274, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1941 June (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - "The Sensational Miss Smith"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 274, Folder 5)
      - Town file, undated (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - "Seven Dreams," town file, 1957 September (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - "Shasta Unlimited"
      - Fire file, 1944 September (Box 275, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1944 September (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - "She Floats Through the Air"
      - Fire file, 1935 May (Box 275, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1935 May (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - "She Just Couldn't Say Yes"
      - Fire file, 1934 September, 1940 February (Box 275, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1940 February, 1963 October (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - "Sheik a la Carte"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 275, Folder 8)
      - Town file, undated (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Shiver and Shake
      - CBS radio show introduction, 1979 June 20 (Box 275, Folder 10)
      - Radio series proposal, circa 1976-1978 (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - "The Shooting Star"
      - Town file, undated (Box 275, Folder 12)
      - "The Shooting Star (Meteor Man)," fire file, 1937 June, 1939 July, 1942 December (Box 275, Folder 13)
      - "The Shooting Star (Meteor Man)," town file, 1939 July, 1942 December (Box 275, Folder 14)
      - "Shooting Star," with penciled revisions, undated (Box 275, Folder 15)
    - "The Signal"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 275, Folder 16)
      - Town file, undated (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - "The Silver Arrow"
      - Fire file, 1937 August (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1937 August (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - "Simple Arithmetic"
      - Fire file, 1937 December (Box 276, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1937 December (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - "Sing a Song of Sixpence"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 276, Folder 6)
      - Town file, undated (Box 276, Folder 7)
    - "Sir Rat"
      - Fire file, 1937 January (Box 276, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1937 January (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - "Six and One" series, fire and town files, 1941 December (Box 276, Folder 10)
    - "The Skeptics Club" series
      - Fire file, undated (Box 276, Folder 11)
      - Town file, undated (Box 276, Folder 12)
    - "The Sky, the Earth, and a Man," town file, 1939 July (Box 276, Folder 13)
    - "Smell of Death," fire file, 1946 October, 1947 April (Box 276, Folder 14)
    - "Snake Charm" See "Snake God" (Box 276, Folder 15)
    - "Snake God"
      - Fire file, 1937 June (Box 276, Folder 16)
      - Town file, 1937 June (Box 276, Folder 17)
    - "Snake in the Grass"
      - Fire file, 1939 October (Box 277, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1939 October (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - "Snake Woman"
      - Fire file, 1937 June (Box 277, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1937 June (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - "So They Got Married"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 277, Folder 5)
      - Town file, undated (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - "Sole Survivors"
      - Fire file, 1935 March, 1939 June (Box 277, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1939 June, 1964 January (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - "Soliloquy with Death"
      - Fire file, 1942 April, 1943 September (Box 277, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1942 April, 1943 September (Box 277, Folder 10)
    - "Speak Artistic"
      - Fire file, 1946 December (Box 277, Folder 11)
      - Town file, 1946 December (Box 277, Folder 12)
    - "Speaking of People" See "Wonderful Day" (Box 277, Folder 13)
    - "Special Day" See "Wonderful Day"
    - "The Spider"
      - Fire file, 1938 June, 1943 May (Box 277, Folder 14)
      - Town file, 1943 May, 1963 May (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - "Spring Picnic"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 278, Folder 2)
      - Town file, undated (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - "S.S. Ugly Duck"
      - Fire file, circa 1941 (Box 278, Folder 4)
      - Town file, circa 1941 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - "Stage Mother"
      - Fire file, 1937 April (Box 278, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1937 April (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - "State Executioner"
      - Fire file, 1937 March, 1939 December, 1943 August (Box 278, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1939 December, 1943 August (Box 278, Folder 9-10)
    - "State's Witness"
      - Fire file, 1937 May (Box 278, Folder 11)
      - Town file, 1937 May (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - "Steel"
      - Fire file, 1939 June (Box 279, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1939 June (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - "Stone Sphere," 1955 March-April (Box 279, Folder 4)
      Time capsule project.
    - "The Story of Alice Merrick"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 279, Folder 5)
      - Town file, undated (Box 279, Folder 6)
    - "Strange Morning"
      - Fire file, 1944 October, 1945 April-May (Box 279, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1945 April-May (Box 279, Folder 8-9)
      - "B To Nyeobichnoye Ootro," Radio P'esa, 1970, 1982 October (Box 279, Folder 10)
        Russian title.
    - "Studio Apartment"
      - Fire file, 1937 December (Box 279, Folder 11)
      - Town file, 1937 December (Box 279, Folder 12)
    - "Sub-Basement"
      - Fire file, 1943 August (Box 279, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1943 August, 1964 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - "Suffer Little Children"
      - Fire file, 1939 June, September, 1941 January, 1943 January (Box 280, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1939 June, September, 1941 January (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - "Super Feature"
      - Fire file, 1938 March, 1943 April (Box 280, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1938 March, 1943 April (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - "Surrender"
      - Fire file, 1944 June (Box 281, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1944 June (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - "Swami"
      - Fire file, 1938 January (Box 281, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1938 January (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - "Talisman"
      - Fire file, 1939 July (Box 281, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1939 July (Box 281, Folder 6)
    - "Task Force"
      - Fire file, 1945 October (Box 281, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1945 October (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - "Ten Grand"
      - Fire file, 1937 October (Box 281, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1937 October (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - "The Terrible Twins"
      - Fire file, 1937 June (Box 281, Folder 11)
      - Town file, circa 1937 (Box 281, Folder 12)
    - "Terror on Main Street" See "This Precious Freedom" (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - "Test Flight"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 282, Folder 2)
      - Town file, undated (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Theatre Comique series, fire and town files, 1935 March-September (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - "These Are Your Brothers"
      - Fire file, 1939 December, 1940 December, 1941 August (Box 282, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1939 December, 1940 December, 1941 August (Box 282, Folder 6)
    - "They Died" See "Efficiency Island" (Box 282, Folder 7)
    - "They Met at Dorset"
      - Fire file, 1943 February (Box 282, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1943 February (Box 282, Folder 9)
    - "They're Here (It's Happening — To Me)"
      - Fire file, 1942 November, 1944 February, 1950 March (Box 283, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1942 November, 1944 February, 1950 March (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - "Thief in the House"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 283, Folder 3)
      - Town file, undated (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - "The Thing," fire and town files, 1943 June (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - "The Thing That Crept"
      - Fire file, 1936 October, 1943 January (Box 283, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1943 January (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - "The Thirteenth Corpse" See "The Bones of Sam Lee" (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - "This Above All"
      - Fire file, 1944 May (Box 283, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1944 May (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - "This African Thing," town file, 1951 February-March (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - "This Is a Man"
      - Fire file, 1944 January (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1944 January (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - "This Living Book"
      - Fire file, 1944 April, 1945 October (Box 284, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1944 April, 1945 October (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - "This Lonely Heart"
      - Gulf Screen Guild Theatre, 1940 January 14 (Box 284, Folder 5)
      - One-hour version, fire file, 1939 August (Box 284, Folder 6)
      - One-hour version, town file, 1939 August (Box 284, Folder 7)
      - Half-hour version, fire file, 1940 January, October (Box 285, Folder 1)
      - Half-hour version, town file, 1940 January, October, 1963 May (Box 285, Folder 2-3)
    - "This Precious Freedom"
      - Fire file, 1939 December, 1940 October (Box 285, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1939 December, 1940 October (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - "Three Brides"
      - Fire file, 1942 July (Box 286, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1942 July (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - "Three Diamonds"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 286, Folder 3)
      - Town file, undated (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - "The Three Good Friends"
      - Fire file, 1937 (Box 286, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1937 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - "Three Matches"
      - Fire file, 1938 April (Box 286, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1938 April (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - "Three on a Ring"
      - Fire file, circa 1938 (Box 286, Folder 9)
      - Town file, circa 1938 (Box 286, Folder 10)
    - "Three Plays about Children," fire and town files, 1945 August (Box 286, Folder 11)
    - "Tiger-Hunt"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 286, Folder 12)
      - Town file, undated (Box 286, Folder 13)
    - "Tin Soldier"
      - Fire file, 1937 November (Box 286, Folder 14)
      - Town file, 1937 November (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - To the President series
      - Opening script of the series, fire file, 1942 October-November (Box 287, Folder 2)
      - Opening script of the series, town file, 1942 October (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - "Tom and Son" See "Christmas Guest" (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - "Tomorrow", Free World Theater episode.
      - Fire file, 1943 February (Box 287, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1943 February (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - "Tong"
      - Fire file, 1936 November (Box 287, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1936 November (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - "Tourist Camp"
      - Fire file, 1934 June (Box 287, Folder 9)
      - Town file, 1937 June (Box 287, Folder 10)
    - "The Trail"
      - Fire file, 1939 September (Box 287, Folder 11)
      - Town file, 1939 September (Box 287, Folder 12)
    - "Treasure"
      - Fire file, 1937 July (Box 287, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1937 July (Box 287, Folder 14)
    - "Treasure Hunt"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 287, Folder 15)
      - Town file, undated (Box 287, Folder 16)
    - "Treasure of Ivory," town file, undated (Box 287, Folder 17)
    - "Trial," fire and town files, 1942 May (Box 287, Folder 18)
    - "The Trial of Dr. Christian," fire and town files, undated (Box 287, Folder 19)
    - "The Trial of Dr. Watson," town file, undated (Box 287, Folder 20)
    - "Trial Son"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 288, Folder 1)
      - Town file, undated (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - "Triple Feature"
      - Fire file, 1945 May (Box 288, Folder 3)
      - Town file, 1945 May (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - "Trouble Night"
      - Fire file, 1937 June (Box 288, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1937 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - "The Truth"
      - Fire file, 1939 April, 1940 January, 1945 June (Box 288, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1939 April, 1940 January, 1945 June (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - "The Twenty Weeks of John Milburn"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 289, Folder 1)
      - Town file, undated (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - "Two Girls and a Job," fire and town files, 1943 September (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Two synopses for radio, miscellaneous file, undated (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - "The Ugliest Man in the World"
      - Fire file, 1939 March, July, 1941 March, 1943 June (Box 289, Folder 5-6)
      - Town file, 1939 March, July, 1941 March, 1943 June, 1963 May, (1 folder) (Box 289-290, Box 289, Box 290)
    - "Uncle Henry and Jackie"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 290, Folder 2)
      - Town file, undated (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Unfinished plays, 1944 January, May, 1945 November, undated (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - "Uninhabited"
      - Fire file, 1937 December (Box 290, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1937 December (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Unknown scripts, fire file, undated (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - "Until Dead"
      - Fire file, 1937 May, 1943 February (Box 290, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1937 May, 1943 February (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - "V-Day"
      - Fire file, 1943 June (Box 290, Folder 10)
      - Town file, 1943 June, September (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - "V-Story"
      - Fire file, 1941 September-October (Box 290, Folder 12)
      - Town file, 1941 October (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - "The Valley" See "The Trail" (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - "Valse Triste"
      - Fire file, 1938 March, 1942 December (Box 291, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1938 March, 1942 December (Box 291, Folder 3)
      - Lights Out episode, town file, 1942 December (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - "Venice in the Morning"
      - Fire file, 1937, 1939 (Box 291, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1937, 1939 (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - "Vicious Circle," town file, 1957 November-1958 February, 1963 May (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - "The Visit," muscular dystrophy, town file, 1959 October-November, 1963 November, 1964 March (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - "Visitor from Hades"
      - Fire file, 1939 July, 1940 December, 1943 July (Box 292, Folder 2-3)
      - Town file, 1939 July, 1940 December, 1943 July, 1963 December (Box 292, Folder 4-5)
    - "Wanted: a Lawyer," fire and town files, 1939 April (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - War chest program
      Oboler wrote radio sketches and produced the radio segment of a program staged at the Hollywood Bowl to launch the Los Angeles area war chest drive.
      - Fire file, 1943 October (Box 293, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1943 October (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - "War Horse"
      - Fire file, 1936 December (Box 293, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1936 December (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - "War News Exclusive"
      - Fire file, 1937 August, 1938 January (Box 293, Folder 6)
      - Town file, 1937 August, 1938 January (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - "The Way Is Clear"
      - Fire file, 1943 September (Box 293, Folder 8)
      - Town file, 1943 September (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - "The Way to Go Home"
      - Fire file, 1942 March (Box 294, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1942 March (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - "We Meet Again"
      - Fire file, 1936 October (Box 294, Folder 3)
      - Town file, circa 1936 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - "Wedding Present"
      - Fire file, 1939 February, May (Box 294, Folder 5)
      - Town file, 1939 February (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - "The Welburns - a Confidential Report"
      - Fire file, 1941 July, 1942 April, 1944 March (Box 294, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1941 July, 1942 April, 1944 March (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - "What the Devil"
      - Fire file, 1942 September-October (Box 295, Folder 1)
      - Town file, 1942 September-October (Box 295, Folder 2)
      - Radio series proposal, undated (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - "What's an American?" sketch
      - Fire file, 1939 November (Box 295, Folder 4)
      - Town file, circa 1939 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - "When Does a Man Die?" undated (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - "Widow Capet"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 295, Folder 7)
      - Town file, undated (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - "Willow's Ark"
      - circa 1965 (Box 295, Folder 9)
      - Boone, 1963, town file, circa 1963 (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - "Woman-Tamer"
      - Fire file, 1935 October (Box 295, Folder 11)
      - Town file, circa 1935 (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - "The Women Stayed at Home"
      - Fire file, 1940 February, December, 1942 September, 1944 February (Box 295, Folder 13)
      - Town file, 1940 February, December, 1942 September, 1944 February (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - "Wonderful Day", Broadcast December 20, 1942, under the title "The Special Day" as an episode of To the President.
      - Fire file, 1942 December, 1943 (Box 296, Folder 2)
      - Town file, 1942 December, 1943 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - "Wonderful World"
      - Fire file, 1945 January (Box 296, Folder 4)
      - Town file, 1945 January (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - "The Word"
      - Fire file, 1939 May, October, 1940 November, 1943 September, 1949 April, 1950 October, (1 folder) (Box 296-297, Box 296, Box 297)
      - Town file, 1939 May, 1940 November, 1943 September, 1950 October, 1963 December (Box 297, Folder 2-4)
    - "Yellow Jack"
      - Fire file, undated (Box 298, Folder 1)
      - Town file, undated (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - "You, My Wife" See "Reno Story" (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - "Young Love Synopsis," town file, 1957 April-1958 February (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - "Young Man of America" series
      - Fire file, 1939 December (Box 298, Folder 5)
      - Town file, undated (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - "Young Mr. Big Shot"
      - Fire file, 1939 November (Box 298, Folder 7)
      - Town file, 1939 November (Box 298, Folder 8)
    - "Your Aunt Emma" series, fire and town files, 1934 (Box 298, Folder 9)
    - "You're My Hoodoo"
      - Fire file, 1936 March (Box 298, Folder 10)
      - Town file, 1936 March (Box 298, Folder 11)
  - Other radio scripts, 1933-1946 and undated
    - "About My Mother," 1942 November 15 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - "Acrophobia," undated (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - "African Adventure," undated (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - "Alter Ego," 1944 October (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - "And Adam Begot," undated (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - "An American Is Born," 1940 November 29 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - "Anna," undated (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - "The Archer," 1943 April 13 (Box 299, Folder 8)
      Lights Out episode.
    - "Jack Armstrong" scripts, with signed letter from Oboler, 1934 June 1 (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - "The Arnelo Affair," 1946 March-August, The Arnelo Affair, a 1947 MGM film written and directed by Oboler, was based on his 1939 Arch Oboler's Plays script, "I’ll Tell My Husband." (Box 299, Folder 10-11)
    - "The Author and the Thing," 1943 September 28 (Box 299, Folder 12)
    - "Baby," undated (Box 299, Folder 13)
    - "Back Where You Came From," 1942 June 7 (Box 299, Folder 14)
    - "The Ball," 1943 March 9 (Box 299, Folder 15)
    - "Bedtime Story — Adults Only," 1946 February 19 (Box 299, Folder 16)
      Three short stories.
    - "Berkeley Square," 1944 February 8 (Box 299, Folder 17)
    - "Big Shot"
      - 1945 July 12 (Box 299, Folder 18)
      - Masculine, 1945 September 13 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - "Bomber to Tokyo," 1942 May 17 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - "Bones of Sam Lee," undated (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - "Brainstorm," 1941 August 27 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - "Bright World," 1941 January 17 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - "Bundles for Britain," 1941 January 1 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - "Cat Wife," 1940 October 18 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - "Escape," 1940 April- June (Box 300, Folder 8-9)
    - "The Family," 1941 February 28 (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - "The Fast One," 1936 October 13, 1943 January 5 (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - "The Flame," 1943 March 23 (Box 300, Folder 12)
    - "The Flying Yorkshireman," 1940 November 15 (Box 300, Folder 13)
    - "Fountain of Dancing Children," 1943 April 4, Free World Theatre episode, 1943. (Box 300, Folder 14)
    - "Fountain of Death," undated (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - "Fox and Hound," undated (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - "Gangster in the House," 1942 May 31 (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - "General Armchair," 1943 June 6, Free World Theatre episode, 1943. (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - "Genghis Khan," 1940 February 17 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - "The Ghost Goes West," 1944 March 14 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Ghost story no. 2, 1942 April 26, October 25 (Box 301, Folder 7)
      To the President.
    - "The Gift," 1940 February 10 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - "Glacier Woman," 1937 September 29, 1943 September 21 (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - "Happy Holiday" screenplay, undated (Box 301, Folder 10)
      Based on "Holiday 194x."
    - "Hate," 1942 March 29 (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - "Have You Seen Him," 1942 March 22 (Box 301, Folder 12)
    - "He Dug it Up," undated (Box 301, Folder 13)
      Empty folder.
    - "The Hero," 1942 December 6 (Box 301, Folder 14)
      To the President episode.
    - "Holiday 194x," undated (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - "Holy Matrimony," 1944 May 2 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - "The House I Live In," 1944 May 30 (Box 302, Folder 3)
      Episode 20 of the series Everything for the Boys.
    - "I Have No Prayer," 1943 February 27 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - "Johnny Quinn, U.S.N.," 1942 February 1 (Box 302, Folder 5)
      First episode of Plays for Americans.
    - "Last Will and Testament of Tom Smith," 1943, Free World Theatre episode, 1943. (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - "Letter at Midnight," 1942 March 15 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - Loose script papers, no title, undated (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - "Lust for Life," 1945 April 12 (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - Mark Twain series, 1-6; The Adventures of Mark Twain, 1-5; The Adventures of Tom Sawyer, #6, undated (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - "Memo to Berchtgesgaden," 1942 (Box 302, Folder 11)
      Episode 3 from the series Plays for Americans.
    - "The Meteor Man," 1942 December 22 (Box 302, Folder 12)
    - "Money, Money, Money," 1936 August 5, 1943 March 30 (Box 302, Folder 13)
    - "The Most Dangerous Game," 1940 March 16 (Box 302, Folder 14)
    - "Mr. Ginsburg," 1941 February 21 (Box 302, Folder 15)
      Everyman's Theater episode.
    - "Mr. Maggs," 1942 December 1 (Box 302, Folder 16)
    - "Mr. Pip," 1939 December 30 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - "Mr. Whiskers," 1940 December 13 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - "Murder Castle," 1946 August 3 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - "Murder in the Script Department," 1943 May 11 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - "My Beloved Relatives," 1942 December 13 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - "The Naked Mountains," 1945 June 21 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - "New World," 1939 December 9 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - "Night Flight," 1943 April 11 (Box 303, Folder 8)
      Eighth episode of Free World Theatre.
    - "Of Human Bondage," undated (Box 303, Folder 9)
      Page 1 missing.
    - "Ostrich in Bed," 1944 March 28 (Box 303, Folder 10)
      Episode 11 of Everything for the Boys.